<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vihaan</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_window">Vihaan</string>
    <string name="skip"><u>Skip for now</u></string>
    <string name="notication">On 19th and 20th Jan 2017</string>
    <string name="notication_title">VIHAAN</string>
    <string name="e">Choose an event</string>
    <string-array name="events">
        <item>Code Trove</item>
        <item>Quiriosity</item>
        <item>Techtonic</item>
        <item>Posteria</item>
        <item>Mega Blog</item>
        <item>Problem Statement</item>
        <item>Freeze The Moment</item>
        <item>App Ki Peshkash</item>
        <item>Introview</item>
        <item>Iotics</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data">
        <item>Are you too sound at cracking codes? Code trove of vihaan brings you a treasure hunt kinda event in which you have to crack current code to get the glimpse of next. Sounds interesting?Participating in it will. </item>
        <item>Quiriosity helps you explore your inquisitivess and gives you the opportunity to answer some of the mysterious questions.</item>
        <item>Are you ready to crack any problem? Techtonic brings you an opportunity to team up and rack your brains and jump to an most appropiate solution.</item>
        <item>The poster presentaion event welcomes you all to display your creativeness and just paint up your artistic imagination.</item>
        <item>Have you ever aspired to be a blogger? If yes,mega blog event helps you to expirence your aspiration brush up your creativeness and explore a beautiful event of blogging.</item>
        <item>Freeze the moment gives you an open opportunity to capture the moment and edit it in best way you can.</item>
        <item>Are you good at making android apps? App ki peshkash is an event which helps you to team up . and create something great,unthinkable application.</item>
        <item>Its a glance of future technology , where there will be a project exhibition </item>
        <item>An interactive session with well known personalities from the industry.</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rules">
        <item></item>
        <item>1.Quiz will be based on technical topics.\n2.Will be held in two rounds,each round followed by elimination</item>
        <item>1.Maximum team of two can be formed,solo entries will be accepted too.
                \n2.Problems will be given on the spot.
                \n3.Will be held in two rounds in first round just a gist of problems will be given, select any one per team.</item>
        <item>1.Topics will be given at the time of regisration.\n2.Maxium team of two can be formed,solo entries will be accepted too.</item>
        <item>1.Topic will be given on the spot.\n2.Only solo entries will be accepted,no team event.\n3.Best blog will be selected and posted on this website.</item>
        <item>
    1.Maxium team of two can be formed,solo entries will be accepted
    \n2.One partner will click the photo,other will photoshop it.
    \n3.Photos to be clicked based on theme which will be provided on the spot.
</item>
        <item>
    1.Only solo entries will be accepted.
    \n2.Participants have to develop app on android studio.
            \n3.hours of time will be allocated.
</item>
        <item>1.Maximum team of two can be formed,solo entries will be accepted </item>
        <item></item>



    </string-array>
    <string-array name="team">
        <item>Team of two</item>
        <item>Team of two</item>
        <item>No team Limit  </item>
        <item>Team of two / Solo entry accepted </item>
        <item>Only solo entry accepted </item>
        <item>Team of two </item>
        <item>Only solo entry accepted </item>
        <item>Team of two / Solo entry accepted</item>
        <item>No Limit</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>
